Catherwood, Martin P. Additional Papers /4041
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Additional Papers
1938-1941
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Catherwood, Martin P.
/4041
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
3084929
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 27, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3025: Martin P. Catherwood Papers
Catherwood, M. P. (Martin Paul), 1904-1978.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3084929
- Planning - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Activities - Division of State Planning (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agenda (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Budget - 1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Garden City Conference State Planning (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Garden City Conference (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Conference on Continuing Economic Studies (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Industrial Studies of NY (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Machine Tool Inventory (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Public Administration Service No. 63 - Governmental Planning Machinery Study (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 1938 Annual Report - Broome County Planning Board (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 1938 State Planning (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Interstate Commerce Commission 1939 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Minutes of the NYS Planning Council (1938) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Minutes of the NYS Planning Council (July 1939-1940) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Minutes of the NYS Planning Council (July 1940-1941) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- State Planning 1939 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Incodel (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Interstate Commission on the Delaware River Basin Annual Report (June 9-10, 1939) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Incodel Business Meeting - 12/1/1939 - Philadelphia, PA (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Incodel (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Interstate Commission on the Delaware River Basin (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Interstate Commission on the Delaware River Basin (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Incodel - September Meeting (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Dual Enrollment in Operating Engineers Apprenticeship and Associate of Science in Engineering (Box 1, Folder 26)
- New York City Office of Collective Bargaining (Box 1, Folder 27)
- The Council: City of New York Local Laws (Box 1, Folder 28)
- A Proposal to Explore Dual Enrollment as an Operating Engineers Apprentice and an Associate of Science in Engineering (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Operating Engineers Dual Enrollment Program (Box 1, Folder 30)